makemoneyapps.com 2017-12-02

# Privacy Policy - THEBILLIONAIRE

Last updated: March 4, 2013

This Privacy Policy applies to thebillionaire.com (“Website”), which is operated by Tricraft LLC (its subsidiary and affiliate corporations, successors, and assigns collectively referred to as “Tricraft”).  Throughout this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) the words “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to Tricraft and its corporate affiliates. By accessing or using this Website or by registering as a member of this Website, you consent to the use of your Personal Data (defined below) as described in this Policy. This Policy applies to all users of the Website, including users who are also registered members. If you are unwilling to consent to our collection and use of your Personal Data as described in this Policy or to accept the terms in the Terms of Use that apply to use of the Website, you should not use the Website. We may revise this Policy at any time by updating the Website.

At Tricraft, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This Privacy Policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Tricraft and how it is used.

**Email**

If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (“opt-in”), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.

We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.  We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law.  Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.

If you want to stop receiving email from us, each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email.

If you have received unwanted, unsolicited emails sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to support@tricraft.com for review.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Websites, Tricraft makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information.  IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Tricraft does use cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Other Technologies**

Other technologies used include clear GIF’s and IP address logging. Clear GIF’s also known as web bugs, beacons, or tags, are small graphic images placed on a web page, web-based document, or in an e-mail message. Clear GIF’s are invisible to the user because they are typically very small (only 1-by-1 pixel) and the same color as the background of the web page, document or e-mail message. We do not use clear GIF’s to collect personal information about you. However, we may use clear GIF’s to capture statistical usage information for our web pages, features, or other elements on a web page. We may correlate this information to a user to personalize user experience and for statistical analysis of user experiences on our web pages.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
– Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Tricraft.  
– Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Tricraft and other sites on the Internet.  
– Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Some of our advertising partners include:  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Clickbank  
Linkshare  
Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Tricraft send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Tricraft has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Tricraft’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Personal Data Submitted by You for Review by other Users**

You post User Submissions (as defined in and governed by the Tricraft Terms of Use) on the Website at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your Personal Data. We cannot and do not guarantee that User Submissions you post on the Website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Submissions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Submissions.

Any improper collection or misuse of Personal Data provided on the Website is a violation of the Tricraft Terms of Use and should be reported to [support@tricraft.com](mailto:support@tricraft.com).

**Children’s Personal Information**

Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act:

•           This site does NOT collect, use, or disclose personal information (including online contact information) of children under the age of 13.

•           In the event that a child under the age of 13 attempts to register on our site, we will NOT accept the registration and will delete information received from the child.

•           In the event that a child posts personal information in a public forum such as a chat room, we will attempt to delete that information once we become aware of it.

**General Information**

This Policy and the Terms of Use shall be governed by, construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of Tennessee, as it is applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within such state, without regard to conflict of law principles. You agree that any cause of action you or Tricraft brings to enforce this Policy and/or the Terms of Use, or in connection with any matters related to this Tricraft Website and/or the Privacy Policy, shall be brought only in either the state or Federal courts located in the State of Tennessee. You agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts of the State of Tennessee for any cause of action arising out of this Policy. You agree to file any cause of action with respect to this Policy within one year after the cause of action arises. You agree that a cause of action filed after this date is barred.

If any provision of this Policy, or the application thereof to any person or circumstances, is held invalid or for any reason, unenforceable including, but not limited to, the warranty disclaimers and liability limitations, then such provision shall be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that matches, as closely as possible, the original provision, and the other provisions of this Policy shall remain in full force and effect. The failure of either party to insist upon strict performance of any provision of this Policy shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. Unless expressly provided otherwise, this Policy is the entire agreement between you and Tricraft with respect to the use of this Tricraft Website and shall not be modified except in writing, signed by an authorized representative of Tricraft.

This Tricraft Website is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of United States of America and is intended for enjoyment of residents of the United States. Tricraft makes no representation that this website is governed by or operated in accordance with the laws of other nations. By using this site and submitting any personal information, visitors from outside of the United States acknowledge the this site is subject to U.S. law, consent to the transfer of personal data to the U.S., and waive any claims that may arise under their own national laws.

**Risk of Loss**

All items purchased from Tricraft are made pursuant to a shipment contract. This means that the risk of loss and title for such items pass to you upon our delivery to the carrier.

**Business Transfers**

We  may  sell,  transfer  or  otherwise  share  some  or  all  of  its  assets,  including  your personally   identifiable   information,   in   connection   with   a   merger,   acquisition, reorganization  or  sale  of  assets  or  in  the  event  of  bankruptcy.  You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this Policy, please contact Tricraft at:

Tricraft LLC  
4636 Lebanon Pike #152  
Hermitage TN 37076  
phone: 615.307.0466  
email: [support@tricraft.com](mailto:support@tricraft.com)
